So maybe, maybe I'll make it a little bit clearer here. So, um, it doesn't matter to me if he really ate down, like he's a really great performer. That's like completely irrelevant. He always eats down.
Do you know? Like, I just, I think, I just want, I just want folks to, to at least be able to acknowledge like, yeah, I watched it because I'm still colonized because it took me a year from seeing Kendrick's performance to see how that was some bullshit too.
Like if you, it's literally the same. It's okay. So people will say, okay, so this guy, Hergan Jeyer, whoever this is, we have to disrupt the system from the inside out where, how, how was bad money on the inside? How was he on the inside? Like someone asked, am I still colonized using Instagram?
Okay. So since you all love to make this false equivalency, let's do it. Instagram is a communication tool that is free and that is accessible by everybody. Okay.
Instagram is, um, Instagram is, um, in the same way controlled by these outward sources. There are ways to manipulate it, to create, um, information, to create, um, communication outside of Instagram.
So it is able to be used as a touch point to other aspects of resistance and revolution. I have yet to be able to see how a Superbowl performance does that. So this is what I'm saying.
If things can be transmutable into efforts of shifting. Someone just asked respectfully, are you afraid of being deported? Let's, let's take it back to another place. Okay. So then you, okay. So people are like, he did not perform for the revolution.
He did not perform for the revolution. The fact that someone literally just said that that bunny performing at Superbowl is performing for the revolution. If he called for a revolution during the performance, then I'd have something else to say. That's what I'm trying to get y'all to see.
Like if you sit at the table and you don't chop the table, then you're just at the table. The table doesn't change. The people sitting at the table doesn't change. Nothing changes. He was not calling for revolution.
The same way that the same way that when Beyonce had dancers in costume, Black Panthers outfits, she was not calling for revolution. And if you're telling me that you felt like he was, there's no, there's no like confusion about a call for revolution.
Like at the end, like at the end, they're dancing around with flags. I'm just like, it is, but it is. And someone says, was that his purpose to do? And in my opinion, where we are in this world at this time, yes, that is every artist's purpose. Yes. Yes. Someone said, now I'm laughing at you. I'm going to laugh at nonsense.
Someone said, you're right. But unfortunately, not everyone is revolutionary. That's irrelevant.
That's irrelevant. At this point, we have to be this. That's what we, at this point, we have to be. It's a Zionist, like a loud Zionist. She was on there wearing a blue dress.
So at the same time, as Latino people were watching, feeling represented, feeling represented, so were Zionists. The same Zionists that are doing all of the oppressing of the Latino people.
They literally had her up there wearing a blue dress to just completely, like, fuck y'all little Latino performance. We in here. She doesn't even make a check. She doesn't even make sense musically to be there.
Like, and so what I'm just trying to impart to folks is that you can, I have to blow my nose. Talk amongst yourselves. Okay, I'm back. I'm going to break it down like this.
I don't think enough people understand. We are dealing with the devil. And we are dealing with something that is beyond the tangible. Okay. And you can read all the books and you can watch all the videos and you can read all the files.
However, I want you to think about, I want you to think about the worst feeling you've ever had. Okay. I want you to think about the worst, the worst feeling you've ever had. I just recalled mine.
That feeling is what the people who are in charge pull from. They have built an entire world based on that darkness for the past 400 years. Okay.
And the only way through is we have to become as dedicated to the pure, to the pure as they are to the dark.
And that pureness is not a disregard of your shadows. It's not a disregard of your, you know, negative feelings. It's not a disregard of your, um, trauma.
You're right. You're right. It is longer than 400 years. You're right. I apologize. You're absolutely right. It's like much longer than that. Um, that pureness is literally acknowledging all of those things and still choosing to uplift light and to uplift life.
However, however, we, I don't know. Someone in here is telling me about taking accountability. However, we have to find what that line is for ourselves and hold to it.
So when we go into spaces that are built on that darkness and we don't go in there with the complete dedication of eradicating it, we are simply feeding it.
That is why I am no longer in Hollywood. That is why I no longer am supported by corporations. That is why I didn't watch the Grammys because I understand that I have to take, I have to take control of how pure my energy stays.
Because we do not need superheroes. Because we do not need superheroes. They have made you believe that superheroes are otherworldly. We are the superheroes.
We have the power within us, but we are so tainted. We have so many extractions that we can't access it.
And the only way I believe to access it is to continuously look it in the, look it in the face, deal with it and remove it.
And sometimes that's coming inward and out and sometimes it's coming outward and in.
And so what I'm telling you may be over some people's heads or outside of their capacity because it's just too spiritual.
People are spiritual. People are spiritual. And that's what I don't think enough people are truly realizing.
These people that are eating children, these people that are sleeping with children, these people that are harming children, they're doing it from a spiritual place.
Do you understand what I'm trying to tell you?
Someone says to me, but he's performing and he's showing colonialism and he's showing, you know, occupation.
And I'm like, yeah, but you're showing colonialism and occupation on a stage built by colonizers that are occupying.
Like that's counterintuitive to me.
That's why I bought my book back.
Because what I look like putting out a memoir about my life, which was attempted to be ruined by Zionists,
with an editor assigned to it, whose name is going to be on it, who's a Zionist?
What I look like, how did I work?
That's why I don't like being referred to as an actress comedian.
Because I have removed myself from celebrity culture.
Because celebrity culture is 1000% responsible for holding us from realizing the stars in us.
So, you know, I had to say to myself, like, I know that you will get money if you put this book out.
You know that you will come up.
You will come up, girl, if you put this book out.
And so instead I had to pay to not put it out.
Things to fight, you have to actually use them to fight.
So when people say like, but you're on Instagram, but you're on Twitter or you're on Instagram or you're on this and that.
It's not like I'm on Instagram.
I'm just dancing around.
I'm not on Instagram pretending.
I'm not on Instagram.
Like, I'm literally using the platform to platform other ways of resistance.
I'm using the platform with the goal of getting us to a point where we don't need the platform.
That is completely different than being on here.
I don't take ads from Instagram.
I don't get money from Instagram unless it's from y'all.
No, he wasn't fighting last night.
And that is not the disconnect.
That is the truth.
He was performing songs that are impactful in a language that the people he's fighting against don't even know.
And nobody watching that show last night can actively say that that show is going to make them come and act different today in the world about resistance than it did before.
I swear to you, no one.
And when someone says resistance looks many different ways.
No, it doesn't.
Y'all love to come up with these really cute little phrases to make your nonsense make sense.
It doesn't look like knitting pussy hats.
It doesn't look like dancing.
I know it doesn't look like singing.
Like, for instance, people standing outside singing songs.
Okay, if you're doing that for your own mental resilience, okay, that is not resistance.
And I know that you think it is, but it's not.
If it is not actively, consistently calling for the shifting of the power structure, then it is not resistance.
Joy is resistance to an extent.
And then at a certain point, it becomes escapism.
I did not miss the whole point.
And I honestly think that you must not know who the fuck you're talking to.
You think that there was a point that I missed, even though it was in the Super Bowl.
You have missed the point.
The other part is that I also understand that everybody is in their phase of metamorphosis, if metamorphosizing at all.
Yes, I have a...
Someone asked, do you have a number of people that have shifted after listening to you?
Tell them, chat.
Have any of you shifted after listening to me?
There's your answer.
Good.
Easy, because that's the goal.
I just want you to rethink your thinking, because they've taught us how to think.
It's not cheesy, it's just carrots.
Facts, Tiffany.
I understand that sometimes we butterflies are having conversations with caterpillar people.
I heard somebody say that, and it's never left me.
And it can feel really frustrating, because you know the...
Not because you want to belittle folks, but because you're like, damn, you could really be a caterpillar.
You could really get in your butterfly phase right now, and it's going to be so awesome.
And the fact of the matter is, we got to speed up the metamorphosis.
You know, if you're comfortable, then you already missed the boat.
Danielle, that's hella funny.
She said, I wish I could eat carrots as a snack.
I feel like I'd be a better person.
Yes, Japan is turning fascist again.
They got that lady in there, and she's shady as hell.
Okay, so here's someone who thinks that they're really telling me something.
Not using the Super Bowl platform like he did would have sullied, would have silenced what he tried to say.
Stop watering his voice with your opinion.
Lots of people felt empowered.
He made his point, because here you are.
I don't know what you think you're trying to say.
What I'm trying to say is that the time for performative performances is over.
That's what I'm trying to say.
The time for it just felt like a good time is over.
Because we can have a good time.
We can have a good time while also being in a place of responsibility for what we're doing.
So, you know, I was a stand-up comic, and I literally had to change where I chose to perform
because I don't want to perform at places that are Zionist.
I can still do the thing that makes people laugh, that gives people a chance to have a good time,
that gives people a release in a space that is not serving the very people I am against.
Other people can't see past celebrity, but I'm going to still say it.
Like, y'all are like, but so many folks really think that representation is resistance.
And really, all representation is, is, it's not even acceptance.
Representation has become compliance.
Is it really, it's interesting to see more of this with Bad Bunny than Kendrick?
You mean in the last year that Donald Trump has been president?
Like, do y'all not understand time and, like, corp?
You know what, I was with my first grade teacher recently, and she was telling me, like,
you know, children don't really understand beginning, middle, and end, so we have to teach that.
We have to teach beginning, middle, and end in stories.
And I was like, how do you not understand beginning, middle, and end?
She was like, what they don't really, what they have to be taught is that there are consequences in the story.
That the beginning happens, and then something happens, and it brings us to the, it brings us to the middle,
and then it brings us to the next thing, and the next thing, and the next thing.
And so I'm just like, how do you look at Kendrick Lamar performing last year,
before the inauguration of Donald Trump, or like right after, and now we're a year later,
and not see that there should be a shift?
How do you not see that?
There is, there is, there have been a series of events that have happened.
And let me just say, for the record, it wasn't cool for Kendrick to perform.
I said that in the beginning of the thing, I realize now, I was bugging.
I was bugging even being like, yay, Kendrick.
What the fuck?
Why are you there, nigga?
But Kendrick was also at the Grammys.
So they always show up.
They always show up.
And at this point, what I'm saying is, this whole dance of like,
we gotta be on the inside, and we gotta be surreptitious,
that's curtains, baby.
Neptune is in Aries.
We are no longer doing the dance of the veil.
The fire horse is coming in rampantly on February 17th.
We are no longer doing performative.
We are no longer doing gradual.
You can't skip steps, but you can speed them up.
It is imperative that we understand this.
We are in confrontation time for the next 14 years.
And we need to confront realities around who the enemy is.
Tell me, was there less crypts and bloods fighting after Kendrick's performance?
You know, for some of us, it felt like, aha, he stuck it to them.
Okay.
They're like, whatever.
And they keep going.
So someone says, Fat Bunny went up in there, and he spoke Spanish,
and he was telling the U.S., you can't suppress us.
Is that what happened?
They're actively suppressing you.
The same ICE agents that are speaking Spanish,
that are arresting other Spanish speakers,
were dancing and enjoying the show the same as you.
Because they also felt represented.
So, someone here put, and, whoosh.
This is why identity politics is a ruse.
This is why.
This is why culture politics and culture wars are a ruse.
Because they don't stand in values.
And when it doesn't stand in values,
it can be shifted and used however the controller sees fit.
Like someone in the air said, we needed Kendrick's performance,
and we needed Bad Bunny's performance.
No, we didn't.
Did you want it?
Fair.
Needed it?
The Obamas were inviting Black people up in the White House.
And I remember feeling so dejected because it was like,
damn, like I've worked all this time,
and I'm still not important enough to be invited.
And I just remember being like,
I just wish I had worked hard enough,
or that I had been like at the level to be invited.
And now, I just feel so thankful to my ancestors for keeping me home.
So that I don't got to be out here telling y'all my bad for going to that house.
Because like Royal Raider here said,
it's an honor that I wasn't invited.
And, you know, this is when I was on Insecure.
Or, no, I hadn't been on Insecure yet.
But this is when I had been doing,
I had just been doing a lot of things,
but I just remember watching and being like, damn.
But now that I really understand what the presidency is,
and now that I really understand what the government is,
and now that I really understand control,
I see that going to those places
is really just no different than like being invited to court by the monarchy.
It's the exact same thing.
It's literally no different.
And then you find out that the monarchy is eating babies.
Someone said, how do you fight the enemy without finances?
The people who have fought the enemy over the course of history have never had finances.
Next question.
It's literally finances that are preventing us from fighting the enemy.
When Val knows it all starts coming at y'all,
I just know,
like,
she gonna come for you,
and it's gonna be accurate every time.
Was my mind blown?
Um, yeah, it was.
I knew that they were harming children.
I didn't know they were consuming them.
You should just be quiet.
The gall of you all blows my mind.
Then what are you upset about, Amanda?
I showed up late.
So then shut up!
Be quiet.
Stick around.
Use context.
Like, who the hell are you?
A party with 836 people and saying,
hey,
you on the staff.
Imagine that.
The gall.
Is it, is it, is it the,
is it the,
the check that has me in that context?
I know what,
I know how that is.
I know how you're saying it.
So then what are you upset about, Amanda?
Like, who the fuck are y'all talking to?
Thank you, Scorpio Show.
It's our drinking water.
There's so much lead.
So, Rick, Rickart, I think,
yes, IG is always messing with my life
because I'm shadow banned.
So,
someone said Armando,
chill on them.
I just want y'all to know that one time
I went to an Urban League conference
when I was in high school
and when I got there,
they could not find my name tag
and it was like a really whole thing
about having a name tag.
Read the comments.
Someone asked something about
people eating babies.
Read the comments.
They're talking about it.
And my name tag,
they could not find it.
They could not find it.
And then they were like,
oh, are you Armando?
And I was like,
I'm Amanda.
And they were like,
oh, here's your name tag.
And it was Armando Scales.
And so I had to walk around
for the whole weekend
with a name tag that said Armando Scales
because they would not give me
a new name tag.
I have no idea why they wouldn't
give me a new name tag,
but they refused.
They would not print out
a new name tag.
My name tag was Armando Scales
for three days
as a 16-year-old.
So someone here said,
Amanda, you always talk
like we're on the same page.
I talk from the page I'm on.
I talk from my page.
You arrive to my page.
Literally, they call it
an Instagram page.
This is the page of Armando Scales.
So you arrive on my page.
And if you are not
on the same page as me,
you get the opportunity
to listen.
You get the opportunity
to disagree.
to scroll.
However, this is literally
my page.
If you come in late
to a conversation
happening on a live,
the best thing to do
is to ask folks
in the live,
hey, what'd I miss?
But when you come in
and you start making
declarative statements
off RIP,
you look a mess.
And this person
is trying to tell me
what I should do.
If you are trying
to reach others,
you should be willing
to articulate
in such a way
that people receive
your message.
The assumption
that people are not
receiving my message
because you are not
is a reflection
of your own ego.
my message is well-received
by enough people.
The action of trying
to get everyone
to receive your message
is disingenuous.
It is literally impossible.
And it is a represent,
and it is an act
of inauthenticity.
I show up as myself
on my page
and you get to choose
how you interact
with my authentic self.
And that authenticity
might be soft and sweetie
and yummy some days.
Some days it might be hard
and in your face.
Some days I might be cursing.
Deontay Kyle discourse
about Black History Month
being only for African Americans.
It is only for African Americans.
Why is that a discourse?
Black History Month
is for African Americans,
but to act like there aren't
other Black people
from the diaspora
involved in the history
of African Americans
is crazy.
That's really the whole thing.
It's this idea
that there's some type
of like pure African American
that,
the idea that there's
some type of pure
African American history
that is devoid
of other Black people
from the Americas
is weird.
I mean, that's just not,
it doesn't make sense.
Louis Farrakhan
is what, Trinidadian?
Marcus Garvey
is Jamaican.
I'm not smacking.
Shirley Chisholm
was Bajan and Jamaican,
I think.
Or Bajan and Ketishan, maybe.
I mean, I can go on
and on and on.
Grandmaster Flash
is Bajan.
Kuhurk is Jamaican.
Waalaikum Salaam, Enigma.
Malcolm X's mother
is from Grenada.
Marcus Garvey
is Jamaican.
Stokely Carmichael
is Trinidadian.
Like,
I think the foundational
African American trend
is a psyop
by the FBI,
created by the FBI
and the CIA
to enforce,
to enforce the idea
that pan-Africanism
is somehow harmful
to the preservation
of a Black American identity.
Those are my thoughts.
Again,
we have to think,
oh, he said
Caribbeans need
to take a back seat?
I don't even know
what that means.
What does that mean?
Caribbeans need
to take a back seat.
Where are Caribbeans
in the front seat?
So here's somebody,
JRS1,
she's not going
to discuss
the clear hypocrisy
with her being a part
of the billionaire system
like Instagram
just like I am
by not deleting my account.
Mind you,
that's literally
how I spent
the first 10 minutes
of this conversation.
But,
JRS1,
you can go fuck yourself
because you have
a fake picture
and a fake name
and it's really easy
to, you know,
stand on fake business
when it really,
literally has
no consequences.
so I hope
your Monday
is off to a great start
of being performative
in your attacks
and maybe
you will put
the same energy
that you just put
towards me
towards the billionaire
class that is
trying to kill you.
Maybe.
And the comedy
that your name
is JRS1,
like,
get your own moniker.
There's already
KRS1.
I know that's why
you have the name
JRS1.
MCs act like
they don't know.
No, you said,
it doesn't matter
what you said before
because then you
attempted to insult me.
So now I'm insulting you
and you can go
fuck yourself.
Y'all love to throw rocks
and hide your hands
because you see me up here
and you want to say
things like,
oh,
it doesn't matter
because you have decided
that because I'm
on this camera
that I don't have feelings
or that I don't,
that I don't incur
any type of
disregard or disrespect.
No,
get the fuck
out of here.
Blocked.
Removed.
Get control
of your feelings.
I'm not even
talking to my mother
because she don't know
how to control
her feelings
when she feels critiqued
for her own choices.
So you think
I'm going to talk
to y'all?
No.
This whole business
of just insulting people
because you feel
some type of way
is out of here.
Stop it.
Yes,
that's Narco 99.
That is a
Hattori Hanzo sword.
Charisma said,
now I got to watch
Kill Bill.
I didn't even know
there were separate
halftime shows.
That should tell you
everything you need
to know about the Super Bowl.
That there are
separate halftime shows.
They were literally like,
we're going to do
a halftime show
for the racists.
That should let you know
that you're used.
They literally said,
that's like paying
slave owners.
That's giving
slave owners reparations.
Like when I heard that,
I was like,
oh,
like,
what,
what?
It's irrelevant
on whether you like
the Super Bowl performance
or not.
That's irrelevant.
Why were you watching
the Super Bowl
in the first place?
What,
like,
why does nothing
mean anything to us?
Why is it so hard
to stand on business?
It's a halftime show.
No,
they had a whole other show
with Kid Rock
and all these other people.
Now that was a smack.
They said that we are
subservient cattle.
It was the head
of Barclays Bank,
which by the way,
got most of their money
from slavery.
Ash said,
took my notes,
headed out.
Barely.
Someone in here,
I feel like,
is Caribbean
because they said
doing all that
marching and carrying on
just to,
just to watch
the Super Bowl.
Exactly.
Like,
what are we talking about?
I'm still trying to understand
what Caribbeans need
to take a backseat means.
I'm just,
I'm never,
it's never,
I'm never really clear
on why it is
so necessary
for
Black American people
to make a
generalization
about Caribbean
Black people
that they do not want
made about themselves.
I've never really
understood that.
That is the language
of the oppressor.
It is so deeply
unintellectual
and
it's just really
counter,
counterproductive
and counterintuitive.
I just,
I've never,
I've never really understood it.
I just don't,
I don't get it.
The idea that
Caribbean people want
Black American reparations
is like,
where,
where have you ever
heard a Caribbean person
say that?
I've just never,
where have you ever
heard a Caribbean person
say we want
Black American reparations?
I've just never heard
anyone say that.
Like,
I've literally
at no point
ever heard anyone
say that.
And the case for reparations
would be on a
familial basis
that is based on record.
So,
I don't,
you know,
like,
when they were doing
reparations,
for land ownership,
disenfranchisement
and discrimination
in Cali,
there were like
stipulations.
Like,
you had to have
lived there
for like 60,
six,
your family
had to have lived there
for like 60 years
or something like that.
Like,
there were very
specific stipulations.
So,
anything outside of that
to me
is just like,
hold on,
I'm blocking
a bot.
Special Order 51
was not 40 acres
and a mule.
It was 40 acres
and it was given out
to a small part
of the population.
It was then rescinded
and it was never meant
for everybody
or for that
particular area.
And it was rescinded
once Abraham Lincoln
was assassinated
and
Andrew
Johnson
came into office.
But one thing
I will tell you
is guess what?
Super Bowl
ain't gonna get us
preparations.
Y'all have a good day.
I will be in
Mississippi
at Jackson.
I'll be in
Jackson,
Mississippi
at Tougaloo College
on Wednesday
and I will be
at the Carver Center
in Alabama,
Birmingham,
Alabama
on Thursday.
Hope to see y'all there.
Bye.